### Contact

585-360-4192 (Work) judydangelo18@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/judydangelo (LinkedIn) www.anchorsaweigh.biz (Company) www.wilsonshepard.com (Company) www.wilsonshepard.com

### Top Skills

(Company)

Nursing Healthcare Nursing Education

# Certifications ANCC

### **Publications**

Health Belief Model
Change...who me?
Allostasis - When Stress Tips Over
Health Belief Model
What is Health Literacy

## Judy D'Angelo RN MSN ARNP LNC CDP CADDCT

Certified Dementia Care Practitioner and Trainer at As Memories Fade

Rochester, New York Area

### Summary

ANCC Approved provider - Wilson Shepard Education Associates is accredited as a provider of nursing continuing professional development by the American Nurses Credentialing Center's Commission on Accreditation.

Recieved certification as a Certified Dementia Care Practitioner and Certified Trainer of Alzheimer's and Dementia. As a legal nurse consultant, I have the expertise as a health care provider and specialized training to consult on medical-related legal cases. I can assist attorneys in reading medical records and understanding medical terminology and healthcare issues to achieve the best results for your clients.

As a nurse educator I am dedicated to delivering academic excellence that supports success. We pride ourselves on personal service to our colleagues. Married...>49 yr

We have had the privilege of providing a superior education to our nation's health care providers. Your continuing education, and the responsibility of preparing you for your future, is our priority.

Judy D'Angelo, RN, MS, ANP, CEO/President of Anchors Aweigh and Wilson Shepard Education Associates providing continuing education for nurses...began this business as opportunity for nurses to enjoy continuing education on Seminar at Sea - and began the concept of the "Home of the Seminar at Sea" in 1989. Since then, the business has grown and now offers specials for leisure travel for customers, and of course, continuing education conferences for her colleagues. Our conferences also include tours to Europe, the US, China, south America. We combine these land tours with visits to health care facilities - to explore healthcare in other countries. Great way to combine fun and education.

Master of Science Degree at the University of Rochester and is now a Adult Nurse Practitioner

"Wilson Shepard is an approved provider of continuing nursing education by The Alabama State Nurses Association, an accredited approver of continuing nursing education by the American Nurses Credentialing Center's Commission on Accreditation." Provider # 5-166

WILSON SHEPARD EDUCATION ASSOCIATES has been approved by the Florida Board of Nursing, Georgia Board of Nursing, and DC Board of Nursing.

CE Provider #: 50-17938

## Experience

As Memories Fade
2 years 2 months

Certified Dementia Care Practitioner and Trainer
June 2018 - Present (2 years 2 months)

Rochester, New York, United States

Certified Dementia Care Practitioner/Trainer June 2018 - Present (2 years 2 months) United States

Our mission is to promote, encourage and enhance the knowledge, skills and practice of all persons who provide care and/or services to those who suffer with illnesses that cause Dementia by means of requiring excellent standards of education, Dementia specific training, and incentives for professional developement of those who are dedicated to the ever growing field of Dementia Care. Join our seminars

D'Angelo Medical Legal Nurse Consultants
Judy D'Angelo RN MSN ANP LNC CDP CADDCT
June 2017 - Present (3 years 2 months)
United States

Our mission is to help our attorney-clients overcome the challenges they may be having with their cases, and assist them in achieving success. Our firm is dedicated to providing comprehensive legal nurse consulting services in order to help keep non-meritorious cases out of the legal system and find the truth within meritorious cases.

D'Angelo Medical Legal nurse consulting assists in the analysis and evaluation of facts and testimony, and the rendering of informed opinions related to the delivery of nursing and other healthcare services and outcomes, and the nature and cause of injuries.

As a company, we provide personalized customer services, prompt communication, and optimal outcomes. In addition to the high quality, affordable services we offer, clients come to us for timely, cost-effective resolutions to their most complex issues.

Wilson Shepard Education Associates 31 years 2 months

Owner

1994 - Present (26 years)

Rochester, New York Area

Providing exceptional continuing education programs for nurses. http://www.wshep.com

#### Owner

June 1989 - Present (31 years 2 months)

Thought about having a meeting, conference at one of the most luxurious all inclusive resorts? We have some special offers for groups. With 15 exclusive resorts throughout the Caribbean, we offer all–inclusive vacations that are as unique as your love for each other. Whatever your ideal romantic getaway entails – adventure in an exotic locale, fun in the sun, peace and serenity or lounging in the lap of luxury – our first class amenities and countless activities make Sandals' all–inclusive resorts in Jamaica,

WILSON SHEPARD EDUCATION ASSOCIATES has been approved by the Florida Board of Nursing, GA Board of Nursing, Alabama Nurses Association, DC Board of Nursing. CE Provider #: 50-17938

"WILSON SHEPARD EDUCATION ASSOCIATES is an approved provider of continuing nursing education by The Alabama State Nurses Association, an accredited approver of continuing nursing education by the American Nurses Credentialing Center's Commission on Accreditation." Approver ID # 5-166

Anchors Aweigh Travel
Founder, Owner
June 1989 - Present (31 years 2 months)
Rochester, New York

Offering affordable luxury travel

Strong Memorial Hospital Registered Nurse October 2000 - October 2010 (10 years 1 month)

Strong Memorial Hospital NP 1999 - 2010 (11 years)

## Education

University of Rochester Masters, Nursing · (2000 - 2004)

St. John Fisher College BS, Nursing · (1997 - 2000)